[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 28, "question": "So how does that make you feel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 29, "answer": "I -- I feel good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ":"], "qSentId": 32, "question": "How many people do you meet on a daily basis that go, you are my hero?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 33, "answer": "A lot -- a lot of people...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 43, "question": "When you get down on those blocks and you're about to explode, what actually goes through the Golden Bolt's mind?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "TO", "VB", ",", "WDT", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 44, "answer": "You -- all you try to do is just relax, really.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 60, "question": "What does it take to be a champion, not just any old champion, to be a great champion?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 61, "answer": "Well, it's just hard work.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 77, "question": "Is it all of it, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 78, "answer": "It's everything.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Johnson"]}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 112, "question": "-- who are your heroes, sporting heroes?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 113, "answer": "For me, uh, Michael Johnson was definitely one.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 166, "question": "And I want to know whether you can basically sing like Marley?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 167, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Marley"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 170, "question": "You've got no game?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 171, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 178, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 179, "answer": "-- I can't really sing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBD", ",", "IN", ",", "CC", ":"], "qSentId": 184, "question": "No?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "aSentId": 185, "answer": "I've tried, though, but...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "DT", "CD", ":", "PRP$", "CD", "JJ", "WDT", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "VBZ", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 186, "question": "Can you do any Bob Marley for me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 187, "answer": "Oh, the one -- my one song which I always sing is like...", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bob Marley"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 202, "question": "Are you going to -- are you going to go for it in Rio?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 203, "answer": "Without a doubt.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 204, "question": "How many -- how many real -- as you sit here now, how many do you think you can race in Rio?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", ":", "WRB", "JJ", "JJ", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 205, "answer": "Well, I've -- well, I've -- I've mentioned this to my coach and I've said it to him.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 217, "question": "ORGAN: These are Puma, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", "VBP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 218, "answer": "(INAUDIBLE) yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Puma"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 224, "question": "Do you wear these?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 225, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", ",", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 228, "question": "Huh?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 229, "answer": "That's the key, though.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2002"]}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 232, "question": "If you had five minutes to live and I had the power to relive a moment for you from your life, what would you choose?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 233, "answer": "World Junior Championships, 2002.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 234, "question": "Why that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 235, "answer": "It was -- it was one of my -- it was a life-changing experience for me in every sense.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 244, "question": "Once?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 245, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 247, "question": "Did she break your heart?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 248, "answer": "Vice versa.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "DT", ":", "PRP", "DT", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 249, "question": "Oh, really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 250, "answer": "We both -- we both had our problems.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 273, "question": "How does it feel to be an inspiration for literally people who are disabled the entire world over, as you are now, thanks to the Olympics?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "NNS", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 274, "answer": "Yes, I think it's a massive blessing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ":", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 307, "question": "It's like of all the things to choose, why that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "VB", ",", "WRB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 308, "answer": "Oh, actually, I met him at the Paralympics, and I watched that -- your interview with him and -- and I had a long chat with him.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 339, "question": "What did she say to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 340, "answer": "She was just crying.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 363, "question": "And do you understand that argument?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 364, "answer": "I'm actually really good friends with Michael.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 412, "question": "So as you -- now you've had time to calm down and reflect on it, what do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "PRP", ":", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "CC", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WDT", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 413, "answer": "No, it is definitely a debate that needed to be brought up.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", ":", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 441, "question": "Are you going to run in Rio?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 442, "answer": "Yes, we're going to -- that's the plan.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 447, "question": "-- since your Olympic appearances?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "PRP$", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 448, "answer": "I haven't had much time to think about that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "VB", ":", "CC", ",", "RB", ",", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 478, "question": "What is the answer?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 479, "answer": "Well, I believe the answer is education and I believe if we can find a way to get the kids to communicate -- and, seriously, arm them with education, then I think they can make the correct choices.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 485, "question": "What is behind this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 486, "answer": "You know, I ask the same question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 492, "question": "What is it about the gun that is so appealing to these young gang members in Chicago?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 493, "answer": "HOMAS: You know, I'm a kid that grew up in poverty, so I understand that, you know, there -- you thirst and you want acknowledgement and power.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Chicago"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 495, "question": "And respect?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 496, "answer": "Respect, power.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 512, "question": "Would you have let him go, if you were -- if you'd still been the Knicks coach?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 513, "answer": "You know, I am so glad that I didn't have anything to do with that deal --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 519, "question": "Would you have sold or allowed them to sell Jeremy Lin if he was playing for you at the time?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 520, "answer": "You know, with such a direct question, I think it deserves a direct answer.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jeremy Lin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 524, "question": "Any plans to come back one day?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "RB", "CD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 525, "answer": "Well, you know, you never say never.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 535, "question": "So the door is open?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 536, "answer": "Well, I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 547, "question": "And the Nets moving to Brooklyn?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NNPS", "VBG", "TO", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 548, "answer": "I like it.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Brooklyn"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 549, "question": "You did?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 550, "answer": "I like it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 568, "question": "Mike, how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 569, "answer": "I'm doing great.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mike"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 577, "question": "You think he's done a good enough job to deserve being re-elected?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "RB", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 578, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 583, "question": "Why are the Republicans so out of touch?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "DT", "NNPS", "RB", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 584, "answer": "We have to have some Republican representative and he has to tell you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 590, "question": "When you go back to your old streets and you meet your old guys and so on, what do you think the real cares and fears of the average American on the street are right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "IN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 591, "answer": "Health care.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 602, "question": "Where is real happiness throughout that process?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 603, "answer": "Real happiness from my perspective, I can only tell you -- as you're asking me, from my ordeals in life and challenges.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 633, "question": "What advice could you give somebody like that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 634, "answer": "You know, I wanted Lindsey to win so bad.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 640, "question": "What does she need to do, Mike, to get out of it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ",", "NNP", ",", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 641, "answer": "She needs a good support system.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mike"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP$", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 646, "question": "Have you met her before?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 647, "answer": "I've met her, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 648, "question": "What do you think of her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 649, "answer": "I think she's an awesome person that's just got to get it together.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJS", "DT", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 689, "question": "Do you still keep pigeons?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 690, "answer": "I have at least a hundred at my house now, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "POS", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 691, "question": "You love them, don't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 692, "answer": "Yes, that's what I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 693, "question": "What is it about the pigeon?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 694, "answer": "I can' tell you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 696, "question": "When you're with them, what do you feel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 697, "answer": "I feel like I'm in heaven.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 703, "question": "You have always been like that with them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 704, "answer": "Always.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 741, "question": "When you hear him talk about what you did to him and for his life, what do you feel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "CC", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 742, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 750, "question": "Does everybody need somebody like a Cus D'Amato to just get a grip of them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 751, "answer": "Listen, I don't know if someone needs someone like Cus.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Cus D'Amato"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PDT", "IN", ",", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 762, "question": "What are you going to do with it next?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 763, "answer": "We're going to go all over, 36 cities across the nation.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 767, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 768, "answer": "The city I did my time in and stuff.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 769, "question": "How will that feel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 770, "answer": "That's going to be pretty awesome.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 785, "question": "When was the last time you put on a pair of boxing gloves?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 786, "answer": "Last time I got my ass kicked.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 790, "question": "If I was to really want to knock somebody out, what is the absolutely best way to do it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 791, "answer": "Knocking out is not necessarily having a hard punch.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 794, "question": "How do you hide it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 795, "answer": "I don't know, you jab.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]